### UNIVERSITI SAINS ISLAM MALAYSIA

# MUHAMMAD BIN AB HADIN

HP: +6017-9643172

960103-03-5109

Email: muhammadabhadin@gmail.com

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia.



#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

I would like to be a part of the company where I could use and enhance my skills as well as acquire work experiences for future development of myself. A Data Scientist with enough upskilling training using predictive modeling, data processing, and data mining algorithms to solve challenging business problems. Involved in Python open-source community and passionate about deep reinforcement learning.

#### **SKILLS**

#### LANGUAGE PROFICIENCY

Malay Advanced
English Intermediate
Arabic Intermediate
Thai Beginner

## SKILLS

Microsoft Office:

Word, Powerpoint, Advanced

Excel

Python Intermediate R Intermediate Power BI Intermediate SQL Intermediate NoSQL Intermediate Tableau Intermediate Hadoop Intermediate Machine Learning Intermediate **Data Visualization** Intermediate Intermediate **Data Mining** 

Intermediate

Intermediate

### **REFEREE**

Data Modelling

Apache Spark

Ahmad Luqman Hakim bin Mohd Yunus Data Scientist Specialist The Center of Applied Data Science +60129724834 luqman@thecads.com

## **WORK EXPERIENCES**

## Apprenticeship

## Center of Applied Data Science

(Oct 2019 - Dec 2019)

- -Used Python and seaborn to scrape, clean, and analyze large datasets -Created machine learning models with Python and scikit-learn to predict the given data with 98% accuracy
- -Conducted cluster analysis to generate segmented data of participants
- -Assisted to build analytic tools to manage data and streamline data analyses using R and SQL Server
- -Conducted detailed industry analyses, research, and drafting reports
- -Developed analytics providing insights on current events in the industry
- -Translated data requirements between front-line consulting staff and technical resources
- -Ensured provision of appropriate analytical support and outcome recommendations for key partners in the business and provide effective project management and delivery of analytics projects

#### Data Co-ordinator

#### **QS Enrollment Solutions Sdn Bhd**

 $(March\ 2020-Now)$ 

-Responsible for processing student data into a usable and acceptable format for input into Customer Relationship Management System (CRMS) in a timely manner and within stipulated deadlines and collaborate with other teams globally to ensure a seamless process in formatting data for inquiry and offer management.

#### **TRAININGS**

#### MOE-MTDC DATA STAR PROGRAMME

- Certification of Professional Junior Data Science

## **EDUCATION**

2019	MOE-MTDC Data Star Programme (Junior Data Scientist) Center of applied data	Certified
2015 – 2019	Bachelor of Science with Honours (Food Biotechnology) Universiti Sains Islam Malaysia	Graduated 28 <sup>th</sup> November 2019 CGPA: 3.01

## **EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES & AWARDS**

- Exco of 'A WEEK TO REMEMBER' (AWTR) for Global Islamic Student Outreach (GISO) to TRICHY, INDIA.
  - Organized and fund-raised a one-week charity trip to Al-Huda Orphanage in Tiruchirappalli, India
  - A representative of the group to present the paperwork to high-ranking student affairs officer of USIM